* *
**
- Okay, Patrick,
one more book,
- 好吧，帕特里克，
又一本书，
then you go to sleep, kay?
- Kay.
然后你去睡觉吧，好吗？
- 凯。
- This one is called
"You Can Be Anything."
- 这个叫
“你可以成为任何人。”
I can be anything?
我可以成为任何人吗？
- Oh, you sure can, pal.
Take a look.
- 哦，你当然可以，朋友。
看看吧。
You can be a firefighter...
你可以成为一名消防员...
- You can be a doctor...
- 你可以成为一名医生...
- You can be a cowboy.
- 你可以成为一名牛仔。
- That's what I want to be!
- 这就是我想成为的人！
- Cowboy. Great choice.
- 牛仔。很棒的选择。
- No, no, no, no, no!
- 不，不，不，不，不！
That.
那。
Buddy, I don't think
you want to be a horse.
伙计，我不认为
你想成为一匹马。
- You said I can be anything,
- 你说我可以成为任何人
and--and I want to be a horse!
而且——我想成为一匹马！
- Sure, sure,
you can be a horse.
- 当然，当然，
你可以成为一匹马。
- Nighty-night, Patrick.
- 晚安，帕特里克。
- A horse.
- 一匹马。
A horse.
一匹马。
Not yet, Gary.
Give me a few more minutes.
还没有，加里。
再给我几分钟。
What
什么
- Meow.
- 喵。
- Oh, horsey!
- 哦，马儿！
Patrick, you were right!
You can be a horse.
帕特里克，你是对的！
你可以成为一匹马。
- Easy there, big fella.
- 放轻松，大伙子。
Easy...
简单的...
Ha!
哈!
- Ah!
- 啊！
That's a good horsey.
这是一匹好马。
Hmm, "horsey."
That's not right.
嗯，“马”。
那是不对的。
You need a name!
你需要一个名字！
I think I'll call you...
我想我会打电话给你...
Patrick!
帕特里克！
- Whoa!
- 哇！
Ride 'em, cowboy!
骑上它们吧，牛仔！
Uh, bucking bronco.
呃，狂野的野马。
- Rodeo clown.
- 牛仔竞技小丑。
* *
**
- Safety first.
- 安全第一。
- Giddy up, Patrick.
- 头晕，帕特里克。
Looking good, Ms. Sandy.
- Thank you.
看起来不错，桑迪女士。
- 谢谢。
And the horse you rode in on?
你骑的那匹马呢？
- Morning, old timer.
- 早上好，老朋友。
* *
**
- Sure, but be gentle.
- 当然可以，但是要温柔。
- He's so soft.
- 他太软了
- What's all the hubbub
out here?
- 到底有什么喧嚣
在这里？
- What the...
- 什么...
So Patrick's a horse now?
那么帕特里克现在是一匹马了？
Ha-ha!
哈哈！
Your phony baloney pony's
你的假胡言乱语小马
more like an old gray mare.
更像一匹老灰母马。
Sorry to say, but, uh,
抱歉地说，但是，呃，
this one's ready
for the glue factory.
这个已经准备好了
用于胶水厂。
- What kind of hub--
- 什么样的枢纽--
What are you doing
violating me personal space?
你在做什么
侵犯我的私人空间？
- Aw...
- He's really fuzzy.
- 噢...
- 他真的很模糊。
- Oh!
- 哦！
Horsey rides!
骑马！
Kids love horseys.
孩子们喜欢马。
Great idea
having Patrick play pony.
好主意
让帕特里克扮演小马。
I'll charge these kids
ten bucks a ride
我会向这些孩子收费
十块钱一趟
and cash in big time!
并大赚一笔！
- Oh, I don't know, Mr. Krabs,
- 哦，我不知道，蟹老板先生，
I think Patrick
will only let me ride him.
我认为帕特里克
只会让我骑他。
Oh, nonsense.
哦，废话。
Pony rides! Ten buckaroos!
骑小马！十只巴卡罗！
Giddy up, Patrick.
Giddy up.
头晕目眩，帕特里克。
头晕了。
- Now, I don't mean to nag,
-现在，我并不是要唠叨，
so don't bridle
when I say this,
所以不要勒缰绳
当我说这句话的时候
but your dream horse
is more like a nightmare!
但你的梦想马
更像是一场噩梦！
Get it?
得到它？
Night
Ha-ha!
夜晚
哈哈！
- Oh, yeah,
now you're feeling your oats.
- 哦，是的，
现在你感觉到你的燕麦了。
Ha-ha! I'm so good.
哈哈！我真好啊
Four at a time
一次四个
quadruplicates me money.
使我的钱翻了四倍。
Let's try for five.
我们来试试五个吧。
- Ah!
- 啊！
- Uh-oh. Ooh.
- 呃哦。哦。
Oh! Ooh.
哦！哦。
My wittle weg!
我的小聪明！
all: Yay!
全体：耶！
All right, next up.
好吧，接下来。
My other wittle weg!
我的另一件小事！
Horsey Patrick, come back!
霍西·帕特里克，回来吧！
- That's me money running away!
Come back!
- 那是我的钱跑了！
回来！
- Oh, yes.
Oh, yes, come back.
- 哦是的。
哦，是的，回来吧。
I said,
"Whoa, horsey Patrick."
我说，
“哇哦，小马帕特里克。”
Look at me, I'm a horse.
看看我，我是一匹马。
Clopity, clopity, clopity.
克洛蒂，克洛蒂，克洛蒂。
Patrick.
帕特里克.
Patrick...
帕特里克...
Patrick.
帕特里克.
Patrick!
帕特里克！
Patrick?
帕特里克？
- Hey, it's okay, boy.
- 嘿，没关系，孩子。
It's me...
这就是我...
- Your old pal, SpongeBob.
- 你的老朋友，海绵宝宝。
Remember?
记住？
- Okay...
- 好的...
Would you like me to whisper?
你愿意我轻声细语吗？
- Nice Patrick.
Pretty Patrick.
- 好帕特里克。
漂亮的帕特里克。
Good Patrick.
好帕特里克。
- Calm down, buddy.
- 冷静点，伙计。
I don't want to lose you again.
我不想再次失去你。
- Whoa! Ow! Ow!
- 哇！噢！噢！
- Aw.
And all this time,
- 噢。
而这段时间，
I thought I was the one
breaking you,
我以为我就是那个
打破你，
but you were the one
breaking me.
但你就是那个
让我心碎。
Patrick horsey, giddy up!
帕特里克·霍西，头晕！
* *
**
- Oh, this is humiliating.
- Quiet.
- 哦，这太丢脸了。
- 安静的。
- Horseys don't talk.
- 马不说话。
Okay, kids, ten bucks a ride!
好吧，孩子们，十块钱一趟！
Who's next?
- Me!
下一个是谁？
- 我！
Get moving, horse!
走吧，马！
- Ow! Cut it out.
- 噢！把它剪掉。
- Wow, Mr. Krabs.
- 哇，蟹老板。
How'd you get Squidward
to give rides?
章鱼哥你是怎么得到的
搭车？
- Hmm...
- 唔...
Says right here
in his contract.
说就在这里
在他的合同中。
"I can work him like a horse."
“我可以像训练一匹马一样训练他。”
- Hey, get your mule away
from my show pony.
- 嘿，把你的骡子带走
来自我的表演小马。
This here's a Thoroughbred.
这是纯种马。
* *
**
- Look at that flank.
- 看看那个侧面。
- Ah!
- Get a load of those hocks.
- 啊！
- 承受这些飞节的负荷。
- Ah!
- 啊！
- Oh, yeah, I'm a real stud.
- 哦，是的，我是一个真正的种马。
- Now look at
your old pile of dog food.
- 现在看看
你那堆旧狗粮
- I'd put my pile of dog food
- 我会放一堆狗粮
up against your stud any day.
任何一天都会与你的种马对抗。
How 'bout a race, then?
那么，来一场比赛怎么样？
First one to deliver
a Krabby Patty
第一个交付的
蟹肉饼
to Black Devil Bay wins.
以黑魔湾获胜。
- You're on!
- 你来了！
- I want a clean race.
No cheating!
- 我想要一场干净的比赛。
没有作弊！
Wait for the bell.
等待铃声。
Ah!
啊!
- Ha-ha! Eat me dust!
- 哈哈！吃掉我的灰尘吧！
- Well, okay.
- 嗯，好吧。
Mmm.
嗯。
Mmm. Hey, your dust
was delicious!
嗯。嘿，你的尘埃
很好吃！
- This shortcut sign
- 这个快捷标志
should send
SpongeBob and Patrick
应该发送
海绵宝宝和帕特里克
far from the finish line.
距离终点线还很远。
- Hi-ho, Squidward!
- 嘿嘿，章鱼哥！
- Whoa!
Whoa, shortcut.
- 哇！
哇，捷径。
This could be a trick.
这可能是一个诡计。
I love tricks!
我喜欢技巧！
- Whoa, whoa!
- 哇，哇！
Hyah!
哈！
Oh, boy, we're ahead!
哦，孩子，我们领先了！
- No, you're actually behind!
- 不，你实际上落后了！
- Oh...
- 哦...
Whoa, Patrick.
哇，帕特里克。
Whoa.
哇哦。
Oh!
哦！
Have some slippery mustard,
slowpokes.
吃点滑溜溜的芥末，
慢吞吞的。
- That was extra spicy
slippery mustard!
- 那太辣了
滑滑的芥末！
- Oh, ratfish!
- 哦，鼠鱼！
I've got one more trick
up me sleeve.
我还有一招
我的袖子。
- This is the police.
- 这是警察。
I'm pulling you over
for speeding!
我把你拉过来
因为超速！
- No, this is the police.
- 不，这是警察。
I'm pulling you over
for impersonating an officer.
我把你拉过来
冒充军官。
- Here's your delivery, sir.
- 这是您的送货单，先生。
I was hungry.
我很饿。
- We win! We win!
- 我们赢了！我们赢了！
- I--I had the best horsey!
I had the best horsey!
- 我--我有最好的马！
我有最好的马！
- I don't want to be
a horse anymore.
- 我不想成为
一匹马了。
Okay, buddy, but remember,
好吧，伙计，但是记住，
you can still be anything.
你仍然可以成为任何人。
- In that case,
- 在这种情况下，
I think I'll be...
我想我会...
a crab!
一只螃蟹！
Ark, ark, ark, ark, ark, ark!
方舟，方舟，方舟，方舟，方舟，方舟！
Oh, no, you don't!
哦，不，你不！
Come back here with me claws!
带着我的爪子回到这里吧！
How 'bout a ride back
搭车回来怎么样
to the old Krusty Krab,
cowboy?
到老蟹堡，
牛仔？
* *
**